stanjamesaffiliates.com 2012-11-18

# StanJames.com - Help: Privacy Policy

## Help : Privacy policy

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data (" **Information** ") and how we will treat it. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 2004 (" **Act** "), the data controller is Stan James plc of 1 The Square, Marina Bay, Gibraltar.

This Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") (together with our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.stanjames.com/help/d.asp?show=standard-terms_sports "Terms and Conditions") and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any Information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us to enable us to manage your relationship with Stan James. By submitting your Information to us and/ or using Stan James' services you confirm your consent to the use of your Information as set out in this Policy.

### Information Collection

We may collect and process the following Information about you:

(i) Information that you provide when registering for a Stan James' account, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for Information when you enter a competition or promotion, and if you report a problem with our Services.

(ii) If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Telephone calls to and from our Contact Centre are recorded for training and security purposes along with the resolution of any queries arising from the service you receive.

(iii) Details of transactions you carry out in respect of our services and of the fulfilment of your orders.

(iv) Details of your visits to our website (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, cookies, weblogs, IP Addresses and other communication data) and any other resources that you access.

### How Information is Used

We may use your Information together with other information for the purposes of:

(i) Setting up and managing your accounts.

(ii) Improving and individualising the services that we offer.

(iii) Processing your transactions and wagers.

(iv) Complying with our duties under applicable law and regulations.

(v) Building up personal profiles.

(vi) Providing you with marketing information and information concerning promotional offers by post, email, telephone and other means. Please adjust your account settings in "My Account" if you do not wish to receive this service.

(vii) Providing you with access to our mobile telephone application when you register an account.

(viii) To help us make credit decisions about you, to prevent fraud, to check your age and identity and to prevent money laundering (we may use third parties for these purposes and these third parties may keep a record of the information).

(ix) To notify you about changes to our service.

### Information Storage

All Information is stored in the database of the company.

We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information is kept secure and protected. We will only disclose personal information to other companies within associated or subsidiary companies and to business partners, successors in title to our business and suppliers that are engaged to process such information on our behalf. 

### Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process Information necessarily involves the transmission of Information on an international basis. Some of the data processors engaged to process Information may be based outside of the European Economic Area. Therefore, by browsing our website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of your Information in this way.

### Disclosure of Information

We are entitled to share the information we hold on you which includes Information and betting history with the regulator and licensing authority sporting bodies and other bodies, including the police, in order to investigate fraud, money laundering or sports integrity issues and to comply with our regulatory duties under Gibraltar law.
